Muhammad Ewies Ahmed

Personal Information

- Ookki Giza (Egypt)
- +2 01011297216
- mohamedeways9@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-eways-535408150/
- https://github.com/mohamedeways
- https://trailblazer.me/id/meways

Date of birth 22/04/1996 | Nationality Egyptian | Military Status: completed

Summary

Sales force Administrator with demonstrated experience in sales force, helping the organizations to improve their business performance and efficiency via the Sales force technology, highly monitor and maintain high levels of quality, accuracy, and process consistency in the organization's business planning.

Work Experience

1/12/2021 Salesforce Administrator Training at Trailhead.

- Design and configure user roles, profiles and permissions, workflow and validation rules, email alerts, field updates, reports, dashboards and other Setup features.
- Create and enhance the pages layouts and Visualforce pages.
- Maintaining the sales cloud, as well as building custom reports and dashboards
- Experience implementing Salesforce configuration changes including Workflow, Process Builder, fields, page layouts, record types, custom settings, dashboards, and reports.

06/05/2018-01/10/2019 Front End Developer

Cloud-11, 6 El-Sahaba Mosque, Ad Dogi Giza (Egypt).

HRMS, Payroll systems.

- Technologies: Html, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap.
- Google Drive: (Private repository).
- Description: HRMS (Human Resource Management System) is a combination of systems and processes that connect human resource management and information technology through HR software.

Recruitment Workflow

- Technologies: Html, CSS, Javascript, Jquery.
- Google Drive : (Private repository)
- **Description:** Recruitment Workflow is a diagram that maps out the sequence of the **recruiting** process, starting with receiving a job requisition and end with onboarding the newly hired employee.

01/02/2018-10/09/2018

Front End Developer (Freelancer)

Upwork

Convert PSD to HTML.

Design website for mobile app.

Education And Training

20/09/2014-20/06/2019

Informationsystem

Faculty of Computers and Information, fayoum (Egypt)

- Basics of Programming
- OOP
- Database Concepts
- Web Development

PERSONAL SKILLS

Job-related skills

Salesforce

- Salesforce.com Administration.
- Business Logic.
- Sales force Lightning Platform.

Front End development

- Html, Html5
- CSS, css3, Sass
- Jquery, Jquery UI Mobile.
- Reactjs
- Git/Github
- Npm
- Ajax, JSON

UI Frameworks

- Bootstrap 3, 4
- Materialize

Programming Language

- Javas cript.
- Apex.
- Visualforce
- SQL Database.

Communication skills

- Management & planning.
- Flexibility.
- Self-learning
- · Commitment and self-discipline
- Teamwork
- Documentation and written skills.

Language

• Arabic: mother Language.

• English: very good.